

CONTACTS

- **\(+38 098 461 7282**
- www.chorny-alexander/
- in Alexander Chorny
- Vinnitsa, Ukraine

SKILLS

- HTML/CSS
 - responsive
 - valid
 - cross-browser
- JavaScript
- Figma, Photoshop
- Git

LANGUAGES

- English Intermediate
- German Intermediate
- Ukrainian Native
- Russian Native

ALEXANDER CHORNY

WEB DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I am a developer with good experience with HTML, CSS and JS. I strive to create reliable, adaptive, cross-browser web products based on best practices and accessibility.

In life, I enjoy self-learning and therefore I try to develop, both in terms of technical skills and communication skills. I feel the need to learn anything new or do something useful in a day. Moreover I like doing sports and developing in various directions: swimming, running, strength training.

EXPERIENCE

JUL 2015 - FEB 2022 MYHOBBY

CONSULTANT MANAGER

Website maintenance, consultations, sales, purchase of goods.

APR 2015 - JUN 2015 APPAREL EXPRESS

IMPROVEMENT OF A WEBSITE

Improvement of website design and functionality. Refinement of the order sorting module.

DEC 2014 - FEB 2015 KRAINEVA ANASTASIA

WEBSITE DEVELOPMENT

Website development for an artist.

EDUCATION

November 2022 - up to now | USA

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

FreeCodeCamp

September 2022 - November 2022 | USA

Responsive Web Design

FreeCodeCamp

August 2022 - September 2022 | Ukraine

HTML + CSS Demo 10

GoIT